listen if you're a coach or course
creator one of the best things that you
can do is create an evergreen lead
magnet for your business now here's the
difference and why an evergreen lead
magnet I think will help again for those
of you haven't met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and for the last 21
almost 22 years I've been in the online
coaching and mentoring space have built
multiple businesses over the $10 million
year mark and I help beginners go from
zero to scaling their business to
multiple six and seven figures using
online response marketing and sales
tactics that work a lot of our clients
get a ton of results better than
anything else that's in the industry and
these videos are designed to help you
even if you're not a client of ours to
get results in your business and so what
we found is is that if people can watch
video content if they can watch some
kind of a video presentation that builds
trust with them to want to become a
client and so if you're selling coaching
or online courses is that if you can get
people to join you for a video
presentation they will become a client
of yours by doing that and so and it's
not just a a sales pitch but it's
actually providing value to people now
whereever green comes in and the
difference is is that what we were doing
is we were hosting a lot of Live Events
and we were doing um challenges to where
people would join us for a live
challenge or a live webinar that we
would host on a specific day and by the
way those aren't dead they still work
but the way that Evergreen works is you
take the same concept of a webinar or a
challenge and you have it be something
that they can watch at any time at any
moment in time and you create automated
emails that go out with an automated
offer sequence to them so that they can
register with you now here's the beauty
behind that and why it works so well and
why I think that every coach or course
grador needs to have this set up in
their business is because it grows your
email list without you having to
constantly be grinding all the time you
can create an offer a lead magnet
something that provides value to people
and they can register for it at any time
at any moment in time you can want watch
some of the ones that I have Below in
the description of this video you can
check out some of my evergreen lead
magnets that I have that I'm running
right now you can literally see exactly
what we're using that have added over 15
new clients to our coaching program in
the last month and you can break down
and even reverse engineer some of the
process of how we do that again I'd love
to see you join me in my client growth
accelerator program in my coaching
program where we help you and come
alongside you and walk you through step
by step everything that you need to do
to be able to build and scale your
business but just go through the funnel
and check out how we do this I think
that having a Evergreen offer like this
a lead Manet it's something that people
can put in their name and email address
and you give them some kind of a video
content of value you in exchange for
that email address and in that during
that content you also get to make a
presentation and a sales pitch for your
main offer for your main coaching
program that you have now you might be
saying well Jeremiah I don't want to
just be selling people I want to provide
value to people and that's great and
that's
wonderful we have to take every
opportunity that we have though in our
businesses if we want to actually make m
money if you're watching this right now
you're somebody who wants to make money
in your business and so if you actually
want to make money you have to take
every opportunity that you have in front
of you to be able to let people know
about what you have for sale to let them
know that you have something for them to
buy otherwise they're not going to know
about it there's a romantic gesture idea
that they're just going to come to you
to your website and they're going to oh
wow I love you so much I want to work
with you that doesn't work it doesn't
work in reality people don't actually do
that and so what we have to do is we
attach a very specific outcome that they
want some kind of problem that we solve
one specific focus and you attach
solving that problem to a video and
during that video content you provide
the value to them for what that is and
then inside of that you're able to take
them on a journey that builds trust with
them to become your client and this is
exactly what we do inside of our
Evergreen offers now the way that
Evergreen Works beautifully is this is
that somebody can sign up with their
name and email address at any time but
we use a little thing called deadline
funnel that attaches a 72-hour deadline
to our offer so if somebody comes in on
Monday they have 72 hours later Tuesday
Wednesday Thursday to be able to make a
decision to become a client of ours and
the beauty of this is is that if
somebody comes in on Wednesday it's
different for every person so if Sally
comes in on on Monday she has Tuesday
Wednesday Thursday to be able to become
a client and then that offer disappears
but if Joe comes in on Wednesday he has
Thursday Friday Saturday to come in and
they see individually based on when they
joined when they came in the offer time
limit as far as that goes and then they
get emails sent to them that have the
time time limit attached to it as well
and so this factor of attaching a time
limit to a value offer some kind of
video value that you're providing people
they sign up to receive this value
you're solving a problem for them and
then there's a limited time offer to
become a client of yours in that now is
every single person going to become a
client no of course not but what you do
is you're seing the idea we have this
program you're letting them know that
you have something to offer and it's
important for you to always let people
know what you have for sale what you
have to offer and then you give them an
opportunity that is expiring to where
there it's not going to be available
forever it's an expiring offer that they
can join you and they can become a
client of yours and they can come into
your
ecosystem during that limited moment in
time and so then if they don't come in
here's the beauty of that you can send
them additional offers you you can send
them another offer next month you can
send them another lead magnet next month
you can send them other video content
Maybe YouTube videos that working really
really well right now YouTube videos
like this you send to your email list to
then provide
value not necessarily a sales pitch like
this YouTube video is not a sales pitch
but it it allows me to provide
additional value to people who are on my
email list who are following me who are
watching me and then over time as we do
that more of those people maybe they
signed up in June and then in July they
watched a YouTube video with you and
then in August they became a client it's
60 days later there's that 60-day cycle
there but there's that nurture there's
that trust build there's that connection
that's established and by doing that by
establishing that connection with the
Potential Prospect by giving them
something of value so they join your
email list and then by continuously
nurturing that relationship with them
that's how we create clients now you
might be saying well Jeremiah you know I
would love to just create one video and
then people just become a client of mine
that's great in theory and maybe 5 10
years ago you could do that but there's
so many different offers and coaches and
mentors and stuff out there that people
do need to start to trust you and it
takes them watching additional pieces of
video content from you whether it be
short form content in the form of
Instagram reels on your Instagram
whether it be long form content on your
YouTube whether it be video
presentations that they're watching
where they're signing up with their
email address and all of these create an
environment a
community that builds an audience for
you and then those people become your
clients if you're just relying on or
hoping that one single offer one single
lead magnet is going to be the end all
be all you're missing it and this is one
of the biggest mistakes that I notic
that a lot of people make is they're
trying to be perfect in that one offer
they're trying to make that one offer
just like be the ultimate thing that
that makes their bank account blow up
it's the ultimate thing they try to make
it so perfect they try to dial it in
here's what works better authenticity
showing up authentically showing up as
yourself to people not trying to be
somebody that you're not not trying to
sound like somebody that you're not not
trying to show up uh as a this version
of you that's ultimately going to gamify
the system and the people are going to
suddenly become clients iers no because
people aren't going to resonate with
that and they're going to recognize that
it's not real that it's not authentic
people want to connect with what is real
and authentic and so when they connect
with that real authenticity in your
videos just be yourself let go of the
facade let go of the pressure to try to
make it
perfect and when you can do that you
will provide people with far more value
you will impact them far more and you'll
close a lot more sales you know as
coaches and mentors I I I see that we
have a duty to provide so much value to
people and to deliver results at every
turn we're not just trying to make money
we're trying to actually change people's
lives and and make it better for them
and make their lives better for them and
and one thing I noticed is we can put so
much pressure on ourselves to try to
look like we're somebody that people
should trust when the truth truth is you
want to know what is
trustworthy is somebody who's just
themselves is somebody who's just being
themselves somebody who's just showing
up authentically as themselves when I
show up in that way I close a lot more
sales than me trying to be this perfect
polished teacher or speaker that's on
here when I'm just myself and I'm just
talking to you like we're sitting across
a a dinner table I'm not trying to make
sure that every little body language and
everything is all perfect but I'm rather
I'm just being me right here we're
talking and I'm delivering this this
content to you and we're having a
conversation that closes so much more on
the way of sales than it all trying to
be perfect and I can look back in my
life anytime I've tried to make
everything perfect that's where burnout
happened that's where the stress that's
where the struggling the communication
style of authenticity is what attracts
people to you and so when we can keep
that in mind when we imagine that we're
just talking to a friend and we say okay
what is a solution that I can solve for
somebody I want you to take a look at
what is your offer what do you coach
people on what do you Mentor them on and
then how can you take one key aspect of
what changes people's lives and teach
that in about 20 30
minutes take that record it on video and
give a little intro about yourself
record that value and at the very end
start to sell people on what your
program is and when you do
this and then you create a page people
can give you their name and email
address they can type it in in exchange
for that you're going to email them the
video to watch it and then over the
course of 3 days after that you're going
to tell them about your program when you
build an offer like this you're going to
grow your email list you're going to get
hundreds of people on your email list
and you're going to ultimately close
more sales than you ever imagined in
your coaching business by doing this now
what I like to do is I like to attach on
top of that maybe some live events that
we might do we might host a live event
or a live webinar to that email list to
the people who already joined our email
list but maybe they didn't become a
client through our Evergreen offer and
this is the beauty of combining in
tandem Live Events with Evergreen offers
and that raises both of them up together
okay and so that's exactly what I help
my clients within our accelerator
program is putting together their offers
putting together their sales copy
knowing exactly what Niche is the most
profitable knowing exactly how do we
promote it how do we get it in front of
the right people and so if you're
somebody that wants to work with me on
that I'd love to see you jump into my
accelerator program and I'd love to show
you how to generate 10 to 20 brand new
clients every single month in your
business you'll find the link below to
be able to get started on that process
and I can't wait to work with you in
there to help you start to get more
clients in your coaching business and
not struggle anymore and start to see
the results that you know are possible
for you so we'll talk soon see you in
the next video have a good one